{
    "id": "c51964d38d6a4a2daf338de131a0830a",
    "title": "General Grammar And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We got a bang …………………….. seeing the movie star.",
            "description": "To get a bang out of something is to be excited about it.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "out",
                "out of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19726ea793d94567b495b93d023bcf8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The trainer backed ………………………. from the enraged tiger.",
            "description": "To back away is to move backward.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8d270ada840474690c0d372c2294779"
        },
        {
            "question": "He never took a ………………………… glance.",
            "description": "Backward can be an adverb and an adjective. Backwards can only be an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "backward",
                "backwards",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a4e3bca5f844102a09c3f316c953b09"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her bad spelling kept her …………………….. becoming a secretary.",
            "description": "To keep somebody from something is to prevent them from it.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "daab064990334b3fa923078531951976"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t feel ……………………… about breaking the glass.",
            "description": "When you feel bad about something you are unhappy about it. ",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "befbd2c1296d46fbba795abee6c1ce2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel ………………………. enough to go to hospital.",
            "description": "When a person feels ill, he feels bad.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6fb557dffdd144ad9bcb9e59a773999a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child behaved ………………………..",
            "description": "Badly can mean improperly.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcf9f3920fbf42c180de8b85cdaa2ab1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She wants a new hat ……………………..",
            "description": "Badly can mean very much.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c85f28d047149d38cffe67825914f54"
        },
        {
            "question": "Customs officers examined all ………………………. at the airport.",
            "description": "Baggage does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "baggage",
                "baggages"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6630b8e697644582b7b213a5955f305c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fishhook was ……………………….. with a worm.",
            "description": "To bait is to allure.",
            "answers": [
                "baited",
                "bated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d87f8a2bac2d428186fd03ba027484d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "We watched the fight with …………………………….. breath.",
            "description": "Bated means lessened or held",
            "answers": [
                "baited",
                "bated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b39b4f03881644a8bf91c78034152e20"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. balance, his accomplishments outweigh his faults.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "On",
                "Upon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c80e6a4def54aea80b8c77c5dae82e8"
        }
    ]
}